const personalityJson = {
	"[None]" : {
		"back" : "",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Abundant" : {
		"back" : "aura_e_emart",
		"front" : "aura_e_emart"
	},
	"Abyssal" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_abyss",
		"front" : "aura_s_abyss"
	},
	"Adamant" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_navy",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Affable" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_xmas_b",
		"front" : "aura_s_xmas_b"
	},
	"Affable Liberated": {
		"each": "aura_s_liberated",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Angry": {
		"each": "aura_a4",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Apocalyptic" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_end",
		"front" : "aura_s_end"
	},
	"Aristocratic": {
		"each": "aura_s_aristocratic",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Arrogant" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_red",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Baleful" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_dark",
		"front" : "aura_s_dark"
	},
	"Bashful" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_whight",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Benevolent" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_pink",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Black Moon": {
		"each": "aura_s_fullmoon",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Black Moon (Fly) [Unused]": {
		"each": "aura_s_fullmoon",
		"back": "back_a_fly",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Blazing": {
		"each": "aura_s_blazing_tenebris",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Blessed": {
		"each": "aura_s_holy_blessed",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Blue Moon" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_moon_blue",
		"front" : "aura_s_transparent_blue"
	},
	"Blue Moon (Fly)" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_moon_blue_fly",
		"front" : "aura_s_transparent_blue_fly"
	},
	"Bold" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_sky",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Brave" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_red",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Brilliant": {
		"each": "aura_a_dazzling",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Bygone": {
		"each": "aura_s_former",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Calm" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_brown",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Capable" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_bluelight",
		"front" : "aura_s_bluelight"
	},
	"Careful" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_black",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Changing": {
		"each": "aura_s_growth_evolving",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Chaotic" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_blackblue",
		"front" : "aura_s_blackblue"
	},
	"Charming" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_yellow",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Chatty": {
		"each": "aura_a_talkative",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Cheerful" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_orange",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Christmas" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_xmas_a",
		"front" : "aura_s_xmas_a"
	},
	"Classy" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_pearl",
		"front" : "aura_s_pearl"
	},
	"Clever" : {
		"each" : "aura_s_smart",
		"back" : "back",
		"front" : "front"
	},
	"Clumsy" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_purple",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Cozy": {
		"each": "aura_s_signature",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Creepy": {
		"each": "aura_s_halloween",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Creepy (Fly) [Unused]": {
		"each": "aura_s_halloween",
		"back": "back_a_fly",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Crimson Moon": {
		"each": "aura_s_fullmoon",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Crimson Moon (Fly) [Unused]": {
		"each": "aura_s_fullmoon",
		"back": "back_b_fly",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Curious" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_green",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Cute": {
		"each": "aura_s_stardust",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Dawn" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_white",
		"front" : "a2_whitegold"
	},
	"Developing": {
		"each": "aura_s_growth_evolving",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Distorted Liberated": {
		"each": "aura_s_liberated",
		"back": "back_c",
		"front": "front_c"
	},
	"Distracted" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_mint",
		"front" : "aura_s_champion2"
	},
	"Docile" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_green",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Dreamy": {
		"each": "aura_s_dreamlike_enigmatic",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Dull" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_babyblue",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Elegant" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_blackhole",
		"front" : "aura_s_star"
	},
	"Energetic": {
		"each": "aura_s_persistent_lively",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Eternal Subconscious": {
		"each": "aura_s_unconscious",
		"back": "back_c",
		"front": "front_c"
	},
	"Excited": {
		"each": "aura_s_exciting_blithe",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Extroverted" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_prism",
		"front" : "aura_s_prism"
	},
	"Familiar": {
		"each": "aura_s_signature",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Fantastical": {
		"each": "aura_s_hopeful",
		"back": "back_c",
		"front": "front_c"
	},
	"Fearful" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_mint",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Frail" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_blackgreen",
		"front" : "aura_s_blackgreen"
	},
	"Friendly": {
		"each": "aura_a_gentle",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Full Moon" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_moon_yellow",
		"front" : "aura_s_transparent_yellow"
	},
	"Full Moon (Fly)" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_moon_yellow_fly",
		"front" : "aura_s_transparent_yellow_fly"
	},
	"Gleaming": {
		"each": "aura_s_glazed",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Glorious": {
		"back" : "aura_s_pvp_b",
		"front" : "aura_s_pvp_b"
	},
	"Gluttonous": {
		"back" : "aura_s_greedy",
		"front" : "aura_s_greedy"
	},
	"Graceful": {
		"each": "aura_s_blessing",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Hardy" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_darkbrown",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Hasty" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_orangered",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Holy": {
		"each": "aura_s_holy_blessed",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Honorable": {
		"back" : "aura_s_pvp_a",
		"front" : "aura_s_pvp_a"
	},
	"Hopeful": {
		"each": "aura_s_hopeful",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Horrendous" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_halloween_b",
		"front" : "aura_s_halloween_b"
	},
	"Horrendous (Fly)" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_halloween_b_fly",
		"front" : "aura_s_halloween_b"
	},
	"Immersed" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_universe2",
		"front" : "aura_s_universe2"
	},
	"Incomplete": {
		"each": "aura_s_incomplete",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Innocent" : {
		"each" : "aura_s_innocent",
		"back" : "back",
		"front" : "front"
	},
	"Introvert" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_red",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Iridescent": {
		"each": "aura_s_luminous",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Joyful": {
		"each": "aura_s_exciting_blithe",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Judgmental": {
		"each": "aura_s_judgement",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Lax" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_pink",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Liberated": {
		"each": "aura_s_liberated",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Lonely" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_lavender",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Longing": {
		"each": "aura_s_admiring",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Lousy" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_navypurple",
		"front" : "a3_purple"
	},
	"Lovely" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_babypink",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Lunatic" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_purplelight",
		"front" : "aura_s_purplelight"
	},
	"Magnificent": {
		"each": "aura_s_grand",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Meticulous" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_blacknavy",
		"front" : "a3_blue"
	},
	"Mischievous" : {
		"each" : "aura_s_stardust",
		"back" : "back_a",
		"front" : "front_a"
	},
	"My Heart": {
	},
	"My Own": {
	},
	"Mysterious": {
		"each": "aura_s_dreamlike_enigmatic",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Mystical" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_greenmint",
		"front" : "a2_l"
	},
	"Naive" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_yellow",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Neat" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_transparent3",
		"front" : "aura_s_star"
	},
	"Noble" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_star",
		"front" : "aura_s_star2"
	},
	"Patient": {
		"each": "aura_s_persistent_lively",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Perfectionist" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_universe1",
		"front" : "aura_s_universe1"
	},
	"Pleasant": {
		"each": "aura_s_melodious",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Protecting": {
		"each": "aura_s_gurdian",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Pure" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_transparent",
		"front" : "aura_s_transparent"
	},
	"Purified": {
		"each": "aura_s_purifying",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Quick Witted" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_yellowgreen",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Quiet" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_blue",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Quirky" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_purple",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Radiant": {
		"each": "aura_s_refreshing",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Rash" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_orange",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Reckless": {
		"each": "aura_a4",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Reserved": {
		"each": "aura_a_shy",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Secretive": {
		"each": "aura_s_arcane",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Serious" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_lapislazuli",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Shadow Moon": {
		"each": "aura_s_fullmoon",
		"back": "back_c",
		"front": "front_c"
	},
	"Shadow Moon (Fly) [Unused]": {
		"each": "aura_s_fullmoon",
		"back": "back_c_fly",
		"front": "front_c"
	},
	"Silent" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_darkblue",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Skilled" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_game_a",
		"front" : "aura_s_game_a"
	},
	"Sky": {
		"each": "aura_s_heavenly",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Smart" : {
		"back" : "aura_b_mint",
		"front" : ""
	},
	"Sociable" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_pastelpink",
		"front" : "a3_purple"
	},
	"Soft": {
		"each": "aura_a_tenderhearted",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Solitary" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_warmgray",
		"front" : "a2"
	},
	"Somber" : {
		"back" : "aura_a2_brown",
		"front" : "a2_copper"
	},
	"Spooky" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_halloween_a",
		"front" : "aura_s_halloween_a"
	},
	"Spooky (Fly)" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_halloween_a_fly",
		"front" : "aura_s_halloween_a"
	},
	"Starry Sea": {
		"each": "aura_s_starsea",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Strategic": {
		"each": "aura_a_strategist",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Subconscious": {
		"each": "aura_s_unconscious",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"Surreal": {
		"each": "aura_s_magical",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Talented" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_game_b",
		"front" : "aura_s_game_b"
	},
	"Terrifying": {
		"each": "aura_s_halloween",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Terrifying (Fly) [Unused]": {
		"each": "aura_s_halloween",
		"back": "back_b_fly",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Timid" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_orange",
		"front" : "a"
	},
	"Tired" : {
		"back" : "aura_a_skywhite",
		"front" : "a3_skywhite"
	},
	"Umbrous": {
		"each": "aura_s_blazing_tenebris",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Unknown" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_universe3",
		"front" : "aura_s_universe3"
	},
	"Upright": {
		"each": "aura_s_robust",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Void Subconscious": {
		"each": "aura_s_unconscious",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"Wild" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_blackred",
		"front" : "aura_s_blackred"
	},
	"Wilderness" : {
		"back" : "aura_s_sunset",
		"front" : "aura_s_sunset"
	},
	"Wishful": {
		"each": "aura_s_wishful",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"Yearning": {
		"each": "aura_s_hopeful",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"(a_apricot)": {
		"back": "aura_a_apricot",
		"front": "a"
	},
	"(a_black)": {
		"back": "aura_a_black",
		"front": "a"
	},
	"(a_darknavy)": {
		"back": "aura_a_darknavy",
		"front": "a"
	},
	"(a_peridot)": {
		"back": "aura_a_peridot",
		"front": "a"
	},
	"(a_vivamagenta)": {
		"back": "aura_a_vivamagenta",
		"front": "a"
	},
	"(a_whight)": {
		"back": "aura_a_whight",
		"front": "a"
	},
	"(a2_blue)": {
		"back": "aura_a2_blue",
		"front": "a2"
	},
	"(a2_darkgreen)": {
		"back": "aura_a2_darkgreen",
		"front": "a2"
	},
	"(a2_darkpurple)": {
		"back": "aura_a2_darkpurple",
		"front": "a2"
	},
	"(s_black)": {
		"back": "aura_s_black",
		"front": "a2"
	},
	"(s_pearl2)": {
		"back": "aura_s_pearl2",
		"front": "aura_s_pearl"
	},
	"(s_transparent2)": {
		"back": "aura_s_transparent2",
		"front": "aura_s_star"
	}
}